crresearch.com 2019-12-06

# C+R Research Privacy Policy | C+R Research

## Who We Are

This Policy describes C+R Research, Inc.'s information collection practices for [www.crresearch.com](http://www.crresearch.com/). C+R Research is located at 500 N. Michigan Ave, Chicago IL 60611. **This policy does not cover information collected offline or elsewhere by C+R Research.**

## What We Collect

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, it describes how we use personally identifiable information about you (information such as email addresses, names, physical addresses, and phone numbers that could be used to uniquely identify you as an individual).

By accepting this privacy policy, providing us with information and by using the Sites, you consent to have your information used as described in this Privacy Policy

## How Is This Information Collected?

We collect information directly from you - for example, when you fill out a form requesting information from us, or register for a webinar.

We also collect information from you passively using our partner’s - Google and HubSpot - 3rd party cookies.

## What Do We Do With The Information?

We use the information we collect:

  1. To understand the use of the Site and make improvements, including system administration or site usage auditing;
  2. To protect the security or integrity of the Site if necessary;
  3. To customize the Site’s content.
  4. To design new products or services, to improve existing products, and to developing advertising programs;
  5. To contact you regarding any problems or questions we have relating to your use of the Site, or, in our discretion, notify you of changes to our Privacy Policy, Terms of Use, or other policy or terms that affect you and your use of the Site;
  6. To respond to your requests;
  7. To register visitors for online activities such as online ordering, webinars, employment applications, comment forms, or any other online or mobile interactive activities and for related purposes;
  8. To send information that we believe you may be interested in, such as information about upcoming webinars, white papers or other of our services, including by email, postal mail, phone, or text message.

## When Do We Share Information?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information (PII) unless we provide users with advance notice.

This does not include third parties providing services on our behalf - such as companies that host our website, help us analyze site data, provide marketing or analytic assistance, etc. so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

When required by law or law enforcement - including at the request of governmental authorities, in response to a subpoena or complaint, to verify or enforce compliance with our policies if we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability or to protect or enforce the rights, interests, or safety of the Site, our users, or others.

Corporate Change - we may sell, transfer, or otherwise disclose user information, including PII, in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, the sale of substantially all assets or of a business group, or other fundamental corporate change.

**Do we use ‘cookies’?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. It will affect the user experience that make our site more efficient and may not function properly. However, you will still be able to place orders.

To learn more specific information about the cookies we use and how we use them please refer to the Cookie Policy section of this document.

## Security

To help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and help ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect.

## Your Rights

You have the following rights, which apply in certain circumstances and subject to certain restrictions, in relation to your personal data:

  * the right to access your personal data;
  * the right to request the rectification and/or erasure of your personal data;
  * the right to restrict the use of your personal data;
  * the right to object to the processing of your personal data;
  * the right to receive your personal data, which you provided to us, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format or to require us to transmit that data to another controller;
  * the right to withdraw your consent to the processing at any time.

If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, please contact us at [privacy@crresearch.com](mailto:privacy@crresearch.com).

## Links To Third Party Sites

Please be aware that when you are on this Web Site or viewing an e-mail from us, you could be directed to other web pages or online content through links that take you outside our service and are beyond our control. These other web sites may set their own cookies, collect data, and/or have their own privacy policies. This Privacy Policy only covers information collected by us on the Sites, and we encourage you to review the privacy policy of any other web site you visit.

## Modification To This Policy

We reserve the right to modify, alter, or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back from time to time.

## How To Contact Us

C+R Research, Inc.  
500 N. Michigan Avenue  
Suite 1200  
Chicago, IL 60611  
312 828-9200  

## Cookie Policy

**Use of cookies**

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. The table below explains the cookies we use and why.

As you browse crresearch.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in.

**Google**

In order to better understand our users, their behavior and to serve them relevant ads about our products we may employ Google Analytics Cookies, and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie).

We have implemented the following: Demographics and Interests Reporting

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**Opting out:**

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the[ Google Ad Settings page](https://myaccount.google.com/). Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page ](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/)or by using the [Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). We use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site.

We also use [Hubspot](https://www.hubspot.com/) to facilitate our email marketing. Hubspot does track your activity on the site.

**Cookie** | **Name** | **Purpose**  
---|---|---  
Cookie Preference | NA | 

This cookie is used to remember a user’s choice about cookies on our site. Where users have previously indicated a preference, that user’s preference will be stored in this cookie.  
  
HubSpot | 

hubspotutk

| 

Hubspot cookies are used to identify you as you interact with the site. By enabling the cookie we can pre-fill certain forms and understand your browsing history.  
  
Universal Analytics (Google) | 

ga

gali

gat

gid

| 

These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our website. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the website. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the website and blog, where visitors have come to the website from and the pages they visited.  
  
Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set, visit [www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/) or [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

Find out how to manage cookies on popular browsers:

To find information relating to other browsers, visit the browser developer's website.

To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites, [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

Opting out of cookies may impede your ability to use certain features of our site including check-out and viewing of on-demand webinars.
